了解Intel 傲腾内存就和做煎饼一样容易
understanding Intel Optane memory is as easy as well making pancakes
不相信我们？
don't believe us?
先把你电脑中的数据想象成摊煎饼的原材料
start by thinking of the data your computer uses as the ingredients you need to make pancakes
把计算机处理器想象成厨子
imagine the computers processor as the cook
DRAM 则作为厨房台面
and the DRAM as the kitchen countertops
硬盘则是出售原料的商店
the store that sells all these ingredients is the hard drive and
并且它是个隔了好几里地的超级大商店
it's a mega store two towns away to get
厨子必须开车到商店去，才能带回原材料
the ingredients the cook has to drive to the store and bring the ingredients back
同时把需要的材料放到台面上，每次都需要做很多工作
to the countertop where they are needed to cook that's a lot of work every time
真是非常费事呢！
you want to make pancakes
现在，如果想要加速这个过程就意味着要增加更多的 DRAM 或者说是计算空间
until now speeding up this process has usually meant adding more DRAM or counter space
但这既昂贵又不切实际
that is both expensive and unrealistic
即使有一个更大更贵台面，你仍然需要去商店才能购买原材料
even with a larger expensive countertop you still need to get all those ingredients from the store
这就是Intel派上用场的地方
that's where Intel comes in
Intel 傲腾内存位于机械硬盘和处理器之间
Intel Optane memory sits between your hard drive and your processor
它有点像厨房边的一个方便的储藏室
kind of like a big convenient pantry right next to your kitchen
Intel 傲腾内存也能被用作系统加速器
Intel Optane memory also used as the system accelerator driver
我们叫这块加速器为“副厨师长”吧！你的副厨会为主厨准备好一切
let's call this driver your sous chef the sous chef gets everything ready for the cook
经过一段时间的相处，你的副厨知道你每周六早上都做煎饼
over time your sous chef learns that you make pancakes every Saturday morning
真棒！！
good for you
你那位出色的副厨会准备好你需要的食材，并将它们贮存在储藏室中
to prepare our awesome sous chef gets the ingredients you need from the store and keeps them in the pantry so
系统加速器会自动学习你的计算行为
the system accelerator automatically learns your computing behaviors
智能识别你最常访问的文件和数据来进行加速
and accelerates frequent tasks by intelligently identifying the files and data you access most frequently
并把它们存储在Intel 傲腾内存模块中
and storing them in the intel Optane memory module
谢谢厨师
Thank You chef
现在你所需的原料或者说数据就在旁边的储藏室里
now you have all the ingredients or data right where you need it in your pantry
因此，你不用再去商店跑一趟了
so no more trips to the store
也就是说，它成为了一台速度更快、响应更敏捷、没有短板的PC
it's a faster more responsive PC with no lag
Intel 傲腾内存可以加速任何一颗第七代酷睿处理器赋能的系统
Intel Optane memory will accelerate any seventh gen core processor based system
在哪里可以得到Intel 傲腾内存加持的体验呢？
how do you get Intel Optane memory
可以在支持傲腾技术的主板或准系统中安装
install the Intel Optane memory module in an Intel obtain ready motherboard or system
或者，你也可以直接从当地的零售商处购买带有 Intel 傲腾内存的整机
or purchase a complete system with Intel Optane memory already installed from a  local retailer
有了它，你就可以在厨房里呼风唤雨
so you can be a beast in the kitchen and achieve dramatically better performance
意味着你的大容量存储介质能获得更好的性能
with all the storage capacity you need
换句话说，你可以好好地吃你的煎饼了！
in other words you can / have your pancakes and eat them too
想获取更多信息，请访问英特尔官网
for more information go to intel.com/optanememory
登~~登登登登~~
[Music]